American Locomotive Company (ALCO) Records
American Locomotive Company (ALCO) Records
- General files
  - Nuclear Energy
    - General
      - A Kaleidoscope of Nuclear Activity, 1960 (Box 18)
      - News Clippings, 1961-1962; 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Niskayuna Rotary Speech, 1961 (Box 18)
      - Nuclear Components, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Nuclear Energy Committee (Box 18)
      - Nuclear Power - Alco Products is There (Box 18)
      - Nuclear Power Reactors - Experience with U.S. (Box 18)
      - Nuclear Progress (Box 18)
      - Nuclear Sub (Box 18)
      - Nucleonics (Box 18)
      - Oak Ridge Nuclear Conference, 1961 (Box 18)
      - Pioneering the World of Nuclear Power, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Polar Regions (Box 19)
      - Power From the Atom is Ready Today, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Power From the Atom Now, 1957 (Box 19)
      - Process Heat Reactor (Box 19)
      - Quality Control - ANuclear Age Necessity, 1960 (Box 19)
      - Radioactive Corrosion (Box 19)
      - Radioactive Nuclides (Box 19)
      - Releases (Box 19)
      - Reprints (Box 19)
      - Small Gas Turbine Reactor (Box 19)
      - Sodium-Cooled Reactor Components (Box 19)
      - Sodium Loop (Box 19)
      - Spectrographic Symposium, 1953 (Box 19)
      - Thermal Expansion, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - U.S. Chamber of Commerce Atomic Film (Box 19)
    - Army Package Power Reactor, 1955
      - General, 3 vols., 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Costs (Box 19)
      - Films, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Hiroshima Peace Memorial Museum (Box 19)
    - Stationary, Medium-Power Reactor SM-1, Alaska, 4 folders (Box 19)
    - Portable, Medium-Power Reactor PM-2A, Greenland
      - General (Box 19)
      - Greenland Power Plant, 1960 (Box 20)
      - Guest Kit for PM-2A Show (Box 20)
      - Publicity (Box 20)
      - Skid-Mounted Nuclear Power, 6 folders (Box 20)
      - World's First Modular Nuclear Power Plant, 1960 (Box 20)
      - Construction of the PM-2A, 1 volume (Box 20)
      - Plant Demonstration-PM-2A, 1960; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - Pamphlets - Conception, Realization, Marketing (Box 20)
    - Portable Low-Power Reactor PL-3
      - Contract Negotiation (Box 20)
      - Contract Received (Box 20)
      - Contract Canceled by Atomic Energy Couuuission (Box 20)
    - Disposal of Reactor-Building Business, 1962; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Criticality Facility Given to Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Ordnance
    - Advertising, 10 folders (Box 20)
    - Advertising Reprints, 11 folders (Box 20)
    - News Releases, 1952-1954; 6 folders (Box 20)
    - News Releases, 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Publicity, 1952-1954; 14 folders (Box 21)
    - Tanks, 20 folders (Box 21)
    - General
      - Administration (Box 21)
      - American Forge and Steel (Box 21)
      - American Ordnance Association (Box 21)
      - Announcements (Box 21)
      - Army Engineering Conference, 1954 (Box 21)
      - Army Supply Contract (Box 21)
      - Attack, Ordnance News Letter; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Booklets and Bulletins (Box 22)
      - Carrier Supervisors' Tour (Box 22)
      - Christmas, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Data (Box 22)
      - Defense Products, 1957 (Box 22)
      - Destroyers, 1942 (Box 22)
      - Final Drive Dispute (Box 22)
      - Fitzgibbons Supervisors Visit, 1952; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - History - Ordnance (Box 22)
      - Labor, 1951-1952; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Latrobe Ordnance History, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Media (Box 22)
      - Missiles, 7 folders (Box 22)
      - Photo Requests, 1953-1954 (Box 22)
      - Planning Together (Box 22)
      - Presentation of Tank Program (Box 22)
      - Reactivation (Box 22)
      - Research, 1952 (Box 22)
      - Security Measures, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Staff Meeting (Box 22)
      - Supervisor's List, 1952 (Box 22)
      - Supervisory Development Program (Box 22)
      - Tanks, 6 folders (Box 22)
      - Time and Expense Reports (Box 22)
    - Photographs
      - Aerial Views of Tank-Testing Site, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Army Ordnance Engineers Conference, 1954 (Box 22)
      - Auburn (Box 22)
      - Balancing Gun (Box 22)
      - Bore Sighting a 90mm. Gun (Box 22)
      - Completed Tank (Box 22)
      - Contact Prints by Lofman, 1952 (Box 22)
      - Conversion of Facilities for War Production (Box 22)
      - Engine Lowering (Box 22)
      - Engine Test Room (Box 22)
      - Engineering and Laboratory (Box 22)
      - Engler (Box 22)
      - Frank Schotters (Box 22)
      - General Urban Niblo's Tour, 1953 (Box 23)
      - Grinding Turret Ring (Box 23)
      - Gunnery Trainer (Box 23)
      - Last Tank off the Niskayuna Line, 1954; 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Loading Tank on Tractor (Box 23)
      - Lowering Turret (Box 23)
      - M-7 Tank Day, 1953; 2 folders (Box 23)
      - M-47 Seen Through Range Finder (Box 23)
      - Manufacturing (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 23)
      - Paint Booth (Box 23)
      - Personnel, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Plant Renovation (Box 23)
      - Positioning Turret and Gun Assembly (Box 23)
      - Press Tour (Box 23)
      - Production Pictures (Box 23)
      - Putting on Road Wheels (Box 23)
      - Rear Deck Grille Assembly (Box 23)
      - Spare Parts (Box 23)
      - Storage Facilities (Box 23)
      - Subcontractors (Box 23)
      - Tank Assembly, 5 folders (Box 23)
      - Tank Shipments (Box 23)
      - Tank Shop (Box 23)
      - Tank Turret Rings (Box 23)
      - Tank at Niskayuna Site (Box 23)
      - Tanks on 45-Mile Run (Box 23)
      - Test Driver - M-47 Medium Tank (Box 23)
      - Testing Gas Tanks (Box 23)
      - Tour of Ordnance (Box 23)
      - Tracking Operation (Box 23)
      - Visitors (Box 23)
      - U.S. Army (Box 23)
      - World War II (Box 23)
  - Personnel
    - Biographies
      - General (Box 23)
      - A (Box 23)
      - Alonso (Box 23)
      - Anderson (Box 23)
      - Austin (Box 23)
      - B (Box 23)
      - Ballou (Box 23)
      - Batts (Box 23)
      - Beardsley (Box 23)
      - Bennett (Box 23)
      - Bierau (Box 23)
      - Byrne (Box 23)
      - Bolte (Box 23)
      - Bosworth (Box 23)
      - Brittell (Box 23)
      - Byrne (Box 23)
      - C (Box 23)
      - Callison, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Chamberlain (Box 23)
      - D (Box 23)
      - Darrin (Box 23)
      - Davis (Box 23)
      - Delamater (Box 23)
      - DeLaney (Box 23)
      - Dellacanonica (Box 23)
      - Dennis (Box 23)
      - Dickerman (Box 24)
      - Donahue (Box 24)
      - Downs (Box 24)
      - E (Box 24)
      - Egbert, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Ennis (Box 24)
      - F (Box 24)
      - Fraser (Box 24)
      - Fryer (Box 24)
      - Funk (Box 24)
      - G (Box 24)
      - Gallagher (Box 24)
      - Gandy (Box 24)
      - Geisler (Box 24)
      - Guz (Box 24)
      - H (Box 24)
      - Haines (Box 24)
      - Harris (Box 24)
      - Homer (Box 24)
      - Hughes, Dana (Box 24)
      - Hughes, Robert (Box 24)
      - Humphries (Box 24)
      - I (Box 24)
      - J (Box 24)
      - Jaeckel (Box 24)
      - K (Box 24)
      - Kasschau (Box 24)
      - Knighton (Box 24)
      - L (Box 24)
      - Lawrance (Box 24)
      - Layton (Box 24)
      - Leggett (Box 24)
      - Lifset (Box 24)
      - Lodge (Box 24)
      - M (Box 24)
      - McColl, 4 folders (Box 24)
      - May (Box 24)
      - Meister (Box 24)
      - Montreal Locomotive Works (Box 24)
      - Morris (Box 24)
      - N and O (Box 24)
      - Naylor (Box 24)
      - Nichols (Box 24)
      - Pittman (Box 24)
      - Prentis (Box 24)
      - Press (Box 24)
      - R (Box 24)
      - Reali (Box 24)
      - Reybold (Box 24)
      - Reynolds (Box 24)
      - Richards (Box 24)
      - Ryan (Box 24)
      - S (Box 24)
      - Schmidt (Box 24)
      - Seifert (Box 24)
      - Sieder (Box 24)
      - Strobell (Box 24)
      - Stromquist (Box 24)
      - Sundberg T (Box 24)
      - Taylor (Box 24)
      - Thompson (Box 24)
      - Townsend (Box 24)
      - Tully (Box 24)
      - U-V (Box 24)
      - Van Valkenburgh (Box 24)
      - Vaughan (Box 24)
      - W (Box 24)
      - Ward (Box 24)
      - Weil (Box 24)
      - White (Box 24)
      - Witherell (Box 24)
      - Young, George (Box 24)
      - Young, Kenneth (Box 24)
      - Z (Box 24)
    - Photographs
      - Atlanta - Brown (Box 24)
      - Auburn - Hutchings (Box 24)
      - Cincinnati - Fraser (Box 24)
      - Dunkirk
        - Alt (Box 24)
        - Clark (Box 24)
        - Kopp (Box 24)
        - Murphy (Box 24)
        - Loeffler (Box 24)
        - Ward (Box 24)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Los Angeles
        - Langford (Box 24)
        - Perkins (Box 24)
      - New York
        - Bolte, 1965 (Box 24)
        - Egbert, 6 folders (Box 24)
        - Geisler (Box 24)
        - Koob (Box 24)
        - Miller (Box 24)
        - Morris, 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Schenectady
        - Bennett (Box 24)
        - Bierau (Box 24)
        - Board of Directors Tour, 1954 (Box 24)
        - Fryer (Box 24)
        - Haines (Box 24)
        - Hughes, Dana (Box 24)
        - Leggett, 2 folders (Box 24)
        - Meem (Box 24)
        - Nichols (Box 24)
        - Reynolds, 2 folders (Box 24)
        - Ryan, Susanne (Box 24)
        - Thomson (Box 24)
        - Van Valkenburgh (Box 24)
      - Allen (Box 25)
      - Austin (Box 25)
      - Board of Directors, 1958 (Box 25)
      - Callison, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Cofrances (Box 25)
      - Corrigan (Box 25)
      - DeLaney, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Dickerman (Box 25)
      - Downs (Box 25)
      - Ennis (Box 25)
      - Fabregas (Box 25)
      - Hanson (Box 25)
      - James (Box 25)
      - Kasschau (Box 25)
      - Miller (Box 25)
      - Naylor (Box 25)
      - Nolan (Box 25)
      - Power Machine Company (Box 25)
      - Prentis (Box 25)
      - Press, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Reid (Box 25)
      - Retired Employees (Box 25)
      - Sawyer (Box 25)
      - Sieder (Box 25)
      - Sundberg (Box 25)
      - White (Box 25)
  - Photographs
    - Aerial Views - Auburn, Dunkirk, Latrobe, Schenectady, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Alco Annual Meetings (Box 25)
    - Alco-Indian Pact (Box 25)
    - Atlantic Coast Line (Box 25)
    - Auburn (Box 25)
    - Auburn Community Meeting (Box 25)
    - Auburn "E" Pennant [Export Flag] Ceremony (Box 25)
    - Auburn Navy Bldg. (Bldg 30) (McIntosh and Seymour Album photographs), 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Beaumont Plant, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Careers Book (Box 25)
    - Chicago Heights "E" [Export Flag] Pix (Box 25)
    - Drilling rig - Power package - Bullard rig installation (Box 25)
    - Factory (Box 25)
    - First Century Locomotive (Box 25)
    - Indians Tour Alco (Box 25)
    - Lake George Picnic, 1957 (Box 25)
    - Labor Negotiations, 1963 (Box 25)
    - Latrobe "E" [Export] Flag, 1963 (Box 25)
    - Miller-Nunlist Signing Alco-Worthington Pact, 1964 (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Modernization (Box 25)
    - Monon Delivery (Box 25)
    - Movotron (Box 25)
    - Niskayuna (Box 25)
    - Research (Box 25)
    - Schenectady "E" [Export] Flag Raising Ceremony, 1963 (Box 25)
    - Travis of D&H for use in an ad (Box 25)
    - Union Pacific Delivery Ceremonies at Omaha, Nebrasks (Box 25)
    - Varanasi (McIntosh and Seymour Album photographs) (Box 25)
    - Beaumont (Box 26)
    - Chicago (Box 26)
    - Chicago Heights (Box 26)
    - Chrysler Tank Arsenal (Box 26)
    - Dunkirk (Box 26)
    - Latrobe (Box 26)
    - Montreal (Box 26)
    - Mounted Slides (Box 26)
    - St. Louis Warehouse (Box 26)
    - Schenectady, 7 folders (Box 26)
    - Schenectady (Box 27)
    - Color Types (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous, 13 folders (Box 27)
    - Negatives, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - St. Paul Railroad Day (Box 27)
    - Photograph Album Pages (Box 27)
    - Photograph Albums, 2 vols. (Box 28)
  - Products
    - General
      - Campbell (Box 28)
      - Century Locomotive, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Cooper Retirement (Box 28)
      - Crawler-Transporter (Box 28)
      - Dennis (Box 28)
      - Diesel-Hydraulic Locomotive, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Erie Mining Project (Box 28)
      - Mead (Box 28)
      - Mediterranian (Box 28)
      - Mattabasset, Connecticut Sewage District (Box 28)
      - Railway Products (Box 28)
      - Product Leaflets (Box 28)
      - Time Magazine Letter (Box 28)
      - Worthington Indian Operations Manager (Box 28)
    - [By year], 1963
      - General
        - Navy Tankers (Box 28)
        - Space Program Transporters (Box 28)
      - Financial, 14 folders (Box 28)
      - Locomotives, Domestic
        - General, 10 folders (Box 28)
        - Atlantic Coast Line (Box 28)
        - Lehigh and Hudson Railway, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Long Island Railway, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Reading Company (Box 28)
        - Union Pacific (Box 28)
      - Locomotives, Foreign
        - Export Award Flag, 3 folders (Box 28)
        - Argentina (Box 28)
        - Asian Railroads-Dieselization (Box 28)
        - India, 4 folders (Box 28)
        - Pakistan (Box 28)
        - Peru (Box 28)
      - Personnel, 18 folders (Box 28)
    - [By year], 1964
      - General
        - Army (Box 28)
        - Auburn Plant Expansion (Box 28)
        - Geodetic Survey Ship (Box 28)
        - New Forged Piston (Box 28)
        - Ocean-Going Tug Fleet (Box 28)
        - Riverboat Propulsion (Box 28)
        - Ship Engines (Box 28)
        - Space Program, 4 folders (Box 28)
        - Submarine Chaser (Box 28)
      - Financial, 13 folders (Box 28)
      - Locomotives, Domestic
        - Alco-Plymouth Locomotive (Box 29)
        - Steam to Diesel (Box 29)
        - General, 11 folders (Box 29)
        - Delaware and Hudson (Box 29)
        - Lehigh Valley (Box 29)
        - Louisville and Nashville (Box 29)
        - Norfolk and Western (Box 29)
        - Pennsylvania (Box 29)
        - Spokane, Portland, and Seattle (Box 29)
        - Wabash (Box 29)
      - Locomotives, Foreign
        - General, 2 folders (Box 29)
        - France (Box 29)
        - Greece (Box 29)
        - India, 3 folders (Box 29)
        - Mexico (Box 29)
        - Peru (Box 29)
        - Spain (Box 29)
      - Personnel, 6 folders (Box 29)
    - [By year], 1965
      - Financial, 13 folders (Box 29)
      - Locomotives, Domestic
        - General, 6 folders (Box 29)
        - Norfolk and Western (Box 29)
        - Spokane, Portland, and Seattle (Box 29)
      - Locomotives, Foreign
        - Australia, 2 folders (Box 29)
        - India (Box 29)
        - Iraq, 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Mexico (Box 29)
        - Pakistan (Box 29)
        - Spain (Box 29)
    - [By year], 1966
      - General, 30 folders (Box 29)
      - Locomotives, Domestic
        - Bucyrus-Erie (Box 29)
        - Monon (Box 29)
        - Norfolk and Western (Box 29)
        - Reading (Box 29)
      - Locomotives, Foreign
        - Chile, 3 folders (Box 29)
        - Korea, 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Pakistan (Box 29)
    - [By year], 1967
      - General, 20 folders (Box 29)
      - New Computer (Box 29)
      - Locomotives, Domestic
        - Lehigh Valley (Box 29)
        - New York Central (Box 29)
        - Reading (Box 29)
      - Locomotives, Foreign-India (Box 29)
    - [By year], 1968; 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Golden Spike Centennial, 1969 (Box 29)
  - Publicity Reprints, 1957-1963
    - Atlanta (Box 29)
    - Civil Defense (Box 29)
    - Corrosion in Diesel Engines (Box 29)
    - Defense (Box 29)
    - Diesel Engines, 9 folders (Box 29)
    - Directors (Box 29)
    - District Offices (Box 29)
    - Executive Mailing, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Forbes (Box 29)
    - Forge and Spring (Box 29)
    - General, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Inco Nickel Topics (Box 30)
    - Indian Railway Engineer (Box 30)
    - Locomotives (Box 30)
    - Lubrication (Box 30)
    - Magnolia Pipe Line (Box 30)
    - Modern Railroads (Box 30)
    - Motive Power, 1876-1951 (Box 30)
    - New Eastern Regional Warehouse (Box 30)
    - New President (Box 30)
    - New Schenectady Facilities (Box 30)
    - Oil Drilling, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Preview (Box 30)
    - Prime Mover Control (Box 30)
    - Rail-Mounted Standby Power (Box 30)
    - Ring Carriers (Box 30)
    - Road Switcher, 5 folders (Box 30)
    - Safety Conference-Occupational Hazards (Box 30)
    - Spectograph (Box 30)
    - Tanks (Box 30)
    - Thermal (Box 30)
    - Tie-Ins (Box 30)
    - Typical Employee (Box 30)
  - Special Projects
    - Alco Automobile, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Gemini Spacecraft, 1965 (Box 30)
    - Offshore Oil Drilling Rig, 5 folders (Box 30)
    - Underwater Tunnels
      - Lincoln Tunnel, New York, 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Sumner Tunnel, Boston, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Speeches
    - Dunkirk (Box 30)
    - Kasschau (Box 30)
    - Leggett (Box 30)
    - Medin (Box 30)
    - Motive Power (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 30)
  - Tax Folders, Mclntosh and Seymour Corporation
    - General, 1914-1917; 4 folders (Box 30)
    - General, 1918-1930; 13 folders (Box 31)
    - Undated (Box 31)
  - Warehouses
    - Chicago (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - North Bergen (Box 31)
    - St. Louis (Box 31)
  - Nuclear Energy Proposal
    - Maritime Gas-Cooled Reactor, 1 volume (Box 32)
  - Nuclear Energy Photographs
    - General (Box 32)
    - Army Package Power Reactor, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Camp Century Installation, Greenland (Box 32)
    - Cerenkov Effect (Box 32)
    - Criticality Facility (Box 32)
    - Nuclear Energy Marketing (Box 32)
  - General
    - Flannery Bolt Company Agreement (Box 33)
    - Indian Railways (Box 33)
    - Land Grant Case-Mohawk River (Box 33)
    - Modern Railroads, 1957 (Box 33)
    - Montreal Locomotive Works: Alco Sells Stock, 1955 (Box 33)
    - News Release: First Diesel-Electric Locomotive (Box 33)
    - Options, Sales, Agreements on Property
      - Schenectady Plant (Box 33)
      - Niskayuna Tank Arsenal (Box 33)
    - Photograph Captions (Box 33)
    - Promotional Leaflets: Locomotives (Box 33)
    - Research (Box 33)
    - Santa Fe Railroad Dinner, 1946 (Box 33)
    - War (Box 33)
- Financial material
  - Depreciation inventories, 1919-1949 (Oversize 1)
  - Federal income tax
    - American Locomotive Sales Corporation, 1913-1919 (Box 33)
    - Ames Pump Company, 1928-1942 (Box 33)
    - Heat Transfer Products, 1928-1938 (Box 33)
    - McIntosh and Seymour, 1912-1913 (Box 33)
    - McIntosh and Seymour depreciation schedules (Box 33)
    - Railway Steel-Spring, 1918 (Box 33)
    - Transamerican Construction Company, 1934-1943 (Box 34)
    - Virginia-American Locomotive Company, 1938-1950 (Box 34)
    - American Locomotive Company
      - [General], 1909-1917; 5 folders (Box 34)
      - [General], 1917-1919; 6 folders (Box 35)
      - [General], 1928; correspondence (Box 35)
      - [General], 1934-1943; 6 folders (Box 36)
      - [General], 1938-1949; 4 folders (Box 37)
    - Railway Steel Spring Company
      - [General, including stocks], 1902-1908 (Box 37)
      - [General], 1919-1922; 8 folders (Box 37)
      - Pullman Plant Sale, 1923 (Box 38)
      - Scranton Plant Sale, 1923 (Box 38)
      - General, 1923; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Hudson Plant Sale, 1924 (Box 38)
      - General, 1924-1930; 1932; 15 folders (Box 38)
      - Ledgers, 3 volumes (Box 38)
      - Ledgers, 5 volumes (Box 39)
  - American Locomotive Company
    - State Tax
      - California
        - Personal Property Tax, 1940-1952 (Box 39)
        - Use Tax, 1941-1947 (Box 39)
        - Dividend Information Returns, 1949-1954 (Box 39)
        - San Francisco Personal Property Tax, 1953-1955 (Box 39)
      - Delaware
        - Steam Locomotive Export Association, Franchise Tax (Box 39)
        - Steam Locomotive Research Institute, Franchise Tax, 1945-1951 (Box 39)
        - Beaumont Iron Works Company, Franchise Tax, 1945-1953 (Box 39)
      - District of Columbia
        - Personal Property Tax, 1944-1954; 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Application for Corporation License, 1949-1955 (Box 40)
      - Georgia
        - Atlanta Personal Property Tax, 1941-1947 (Box 40)
        - Annual Registration of a Corporation, 1941-1954 (Box 40)
        - Personal Property Taxes-Atlanta, 1942-1949 (Box 40)
      - Illinois
        - Annual Report, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Cook County Personal Property Tax, 1945-1954; 4 folders (Box 40)
        - Retailers' Occupation Tax, 1938-1946; 3 folders (Box 40)
      - Kansas, Compensating Use Tax, 1945-1946 (Box 40)
      - Missouri
        - General (Box 40)
        - St. Louis Personal Property Tax (Box 40)
        - St. Louis Property Tax, 1947-1954 (Box 41)
        - Registration and Anti-Trust Affidavit, 1948-1954 (Box 41)
        - Franchise Tax, 1948-1960 (Box 41)
      - New York
        - Montreal Locomotive Works, 1942-1954; 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Steam Locomotive Research Institute, 1944-1952; 3 folders (Box 41)
      - New York City
        - Gross Receipts Tax, 1945-1953; 5 folders (Box 41)
        - Occupancy Tax, 1941-1954; 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Sales and Use Tax, 1936-1949; 4 folders (Box 41)
      - Ohio
        - Cleveland Personal Property Tax, 1941-1953 (Box 41)
        - Stockholders, 1952-1955 (Box 41)
      - Pennsylvania, 1939-1940 (Box 41)
      - Seattle, Washington: Application for Business License, 1953-1954 (Box 42)
      - Texas
        - General, 1945-1954 (Box 42)
        - Beaumont Iron Works, 1946-1954; 5 folders (Box 42)
      - Virginia, 1942-1954; 4 folders (Box 42)
      - Washington State, 1951-1954; 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Federal Corporation Tax
      - [General], 1909-1917; 9 folders (Box 42)
      - Tax Refund Claim, 1917-1918; 2 folders (Box 42)
      - [General], 1917-1920; 1929-1943; 8 folders (Box 43)
    - Tax forms, 1940-1947; 14 folders (Box 43)
    - Federal Excise Tax, 10 folders (Box 43)
    - Federal Excise Tax, 10 folders (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Canadian Tax Forms, 1946-1947; 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Personal Income Tax-Administrators
      - Canadian
        - Gardner (Box 44)
        - Perkins (Box 44)
      - Brockman (Box 44)
      - Cooley (Box 44)
      - Daniel (Box 44)
      - Dietrick (Box 44)
      - Eycleshimer, 1942 (Box 44)
      - Haley, 1942 (Box 44)
      - Lambert, 1942 (Box 44)
      - Rockenstire, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Steele (Box 45)
      - Van Valkenburgh (Box 45)
      - Welton (Box 45)
      - Wiese (Box 45)
    - Depreciation
      - Memorandum (Box 45)
      - [General], 1926-1931; 1937-1945; 5 folders (Box 45)
      - 1945-East Side Building (Box 45)
      - General, 1946 (Box 45)
      - Retirements, 1946 (Box 45)
      - Property, 1946 (Box 45)
      - [General], 1947-1949; 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Losses, 1949 (Box 45)
    - Financial schedules, 1941-1953; 12 folders (Box 45)
    - Financial schedules, 1954-1955; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Deeds and properties
      - Ballston Spa, 1930 (Box 46)
      - Chattel Mortgage, 1927 (Box 46)
      - Peek Street Lot-Schenectady, 1942 (Box 46)
      - Schenectady, 1916; 1937,; 1942; 3 folders (Box 46)
    - General
      - Canadian Insurance Tax (Box 46)
      - Certificate of Incorporation, 1901 (Box 46)
      - Credit for Foreign Taxes Paid (Box 46)
      - Decisions of Comptroller General (Box 46)
      - Detail of Engines Sold Under Lease and Lien Agreements (Box 46)
      - Flannery Bolt Company (Box 46)
      - General (Box 46)
      - Inventory (Box 46)
      - Investments (Box 46)
      - Miscellaneous Data (Box 46)
      - Old Analysis of Reserve Accounts (Box 47)
      - Sale of Pittsburgh and Cooke Works (Box 47)
      - Statistics (Box 47)
      - Tax Services (Box 47)
      - City Taxes, 1938 (Box 47)
      - Foreign Taxes, 1945 (Box 47)
      - Balance Sheets, 1950; 1951,; 1952; 3 folders (Box 47)
      - Profit and Loss Statements, 1950; 1951,; 1952; 3 folders (Box 47)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1955 (Box 47)